<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academie Heroica on Art of the Possible</title>
    <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academie Heroica on Art of the Possible</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:02:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The World of Heroica</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/1-heroica/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/1-heroica/</guid>
      <description>Heroica is a verdant world with high magic potential and naturally occuring portals to other worlds through points of great natural beauty and power (waterfalls, mountains, ocean depths, caverns. Portals can also occur close to extremely powerful animals, monsters, spirits and gods.&#xA;Portals The portals to the near worlds are open - which means lots of people know about them and anyone can use them to travel. There are also secret portals that require a special key to use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academie Heroica - Teachers</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/2_5-teachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 11:02:58 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/2_5-teachers/</guid>
      <description>Teachers The faculty of the Academie were all heroes in their own right from across worlds both near and far. They now dedicate themselves to training the heroes of the future. They are highly capable and&amp;hellip; unique individuals.&#xA;Most teachers will be Level 5-6, but might be level 7 or 8 in their areas of specialty.&#xA;Merlin - An ancient, slightly mad and powerful wizard and the principal of Lycee Heroica</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hero School - Academie Heroica</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/2-hero_school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 11:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/2-hero_school/</guid>
      <description>The Hero School - Lycée Heroica As a natural interdimensional crossroads, Heroica is the natural place to grow and educate the heroes that each world will need to protect its peace, people and environment. Talented youth for hundreds of worlds come to the Lycee every year to learn from and with the best of the best.&#xA;Training heroes begins very young in most worlds. Children start learning their trade and developing their skills and powers from age 5 or 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academie Grounds</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/3-grounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 12:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/3-grounds/</guid>
      <description>The Grounds Dormatories - many students go back to their home world after school, buy many especially from the Far Worlds, do not. The dorms are a fun, friendly and welcoming space for young heroes to live and learn. The Radzone - a dangerous desert training zone with robots and irradiated scorpions The Chapel - a place of learning, contemplation and study The Magic Forest - a great place to practice fighting monsters, fending off scary spirits and surviving in the worlds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classes and Curriculum</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/4-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 13:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/4-classes/</guid>
      <description>Classes and Curriculum A quick overview of the first year classes and some ideas for each.&#xA;Exploring Ruins and Finding Treasure Teacher: Portia - a Curious Cat who Moves with Grace&#xA;Exploring dark tunnels Traps and avoiding them Mysterious puzzles Ancient relics Fighting Bad Guys and Battles Teacher: Sir Graven - A Weathered Knight who Fights to the End&#xA;Duels Street skirmishes Large battles Space battles Guerilla fighting Fantastic environments / Set battles Different locations Different scenarios Being Sneaky Sneaking around Being one with the night Escaping with hostages Surveillance and shadowing Disguise Undercover work Spy-craft Bugs, divination and cameras Solving Puzzles - Teacher: Nimue - A Tricky Sphinx who Talks in Riddles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Students</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/5-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/5-students/</guid>
      <description>The Students Bartleby - Clumsy but Brave Knight who Rides Like the Wind (L4) Courageous, but unsure of himself Tall boy, thin and a little bit clumsy Skilled at combat and taking hits Plate mail, sword and shield Flying Horse named Eggo Keely - Curious Explorer Tomb Raider who Would Rather be Reading a Book (L4) Tall black girl with long braids and an intelligent smile Knows a lot about treasures and old legends Uses a bow and likes running and jumping Has a pet Monkey named Ziggy who collects socks Xiu Xeng - Charismatic Wizard who Talks to Spirits (L4) Short Chinese girl who is very athletic and good at soccer Has a big smile and a warm heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Near Worlds</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/6-near_worlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 15:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/6-near_worlds/</guid>
      <description>The Near Worlds Some worlds are closer than others. Your young hero will likely come from one of these near worlds. If nothing here strikes your fancy, create a new world, name it and give it a short description and away you go.&#xA;Fantasia A world of heroic warriors, rogues, wizards and clerics, knights, dragons, quests and peril. There are a few huge cities, but outside of them lies a vast world of adventure and danger with small points of light and civilization struggling to survive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academie Villainous</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/7-academie_villainous/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 16:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/7-academie_villainous/</guid>
      <description>Académie Villainous A secret school that recruits, trains and operates in the shadows, the Académie Villainous is the dark twin to the Hero School. The children and families of the multiverses greatest villains study here and prepare to do battle with and outwit their nemeses: your heroes!&#xA;Teachers Black Eye - Teacher - Black cat with four heads and four tails. Lives in a big haunted castle. Galopin Chatece - team of ninja, many different types - group of three - minions for a student Harry Quinn - Skelton Warrior Students </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Rules</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/8-game_rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 17:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/8-game_rules/</guid>
      <description>Game Rules Going for a mix between Cypher System and Nights Black Agents here.&#xA;Grade and Experience Your grade is your level in Academie Heroica and shows how much Effort you can use to make a challenge easier. It starts at 1. You improve your grade through experience. You&amp;rsquo;ll normally get between 2 and 4 experience for each session you play depending on how much fun you have, how much cool stuff you do and how much you learn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adventure - Welcome to Heroica</title>
      <link>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/9-adventures/9-welcome_to_heroica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 18:02:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://toferc.github.io/posts/academie_heroica/9-adventures/9-welcome_to_heroica/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Academie Heroica! Heroes are have just graduated from their home town schools Grade 3 and are starting as Grade 1 Academie Heroica students! They are welcomed to the school. It looks like a massive playground with different cultures and realities all winding around each other. Heroes will see: Unicorns walking on rainbows Talking cats and animals Kids riding flying skateboards Robots and spaceships People practicing magic The new students meet their homeroom teacher for class 1-A.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
